<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maltz English CEFR English assessment on Maltz English - CEFR English Assessment</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maltz English CEFR English assessment on Maltz English - CEFR English Assessment</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Certificate</title>
      <link>/cert/h4T3o/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cert/h4T3o/</guid>
      <description>This is to certify that John Doe  has successfully completed the Certificate and earned English level:  Awarded on: 8 Jun 2018   Understanding the results  MaltzEnglish SET 1-30 31-40 41-50 51-60 61-70 71-100   CEFR  A1 Beginner   A2 Elementary  B1 Intermediate   B2 Upper Intermediate   C1 Advanced   C2 Proficient     MaltzEnglish SET CEFR   1-30  A1 Beginner    31-40  A2 Elementary    41-50 B1 Intermediate    51-60  B2 Upper Intermediate    61-70  C1 Advanced    71-100  C2 Proficient    The achieved English level is 45/100 on the MaltzEnglish SET score scale and B1 Intermediate according to the Common European Framework of Reference (CEFR).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/faq/</guid>
      <description>About Maltz English  General Information  What is the Maltz English Standard English Test?  The Maltz Online Standard English Test (ME SET) is a free, online English test designed to meet the high technical standards as the other standardized tests in the field, such as the TOEFL or IELTS.
With the Maltz Standard English Test, we set out to challenge the status quo – to build a testing solution that not only provides reliable measurement, but is also affordable, simple to use, and always accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Group plan</title>
      <link>/intensive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intensive/</guid>
      <description>INTENSIVE Plan / three times per week   INTENSIVE PLAN   Forming study groups is a very effective strategy for enhancing learning. Groups share unique insights and learn from each other.    INTENSIVE PLAN  Improve your level of English proficiency, three times per week with personal trainer from USA, UK or South Africa. Get started!   $168/month (cancel anytime)    25-minute lessons    Monthly assessments    Easily fits your personal schedule    All teachers are native speakers, experienced &amp; certified    Homework assigned by your teacher after each lesson      Recommended if you want to quickly assess your English skills, both reading and listening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linkedin</title>
      <link>/linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Add to LinkedIn Profile   Add your Maltz English Certificate to your LinkedIn Profile  With completion of your Maltz English assessment, you will receive a personalized, official English certificate (view example). You can easily add your Certificate URL to your LinkedIn profile - in 3 easy steps!   Step 1:Schedule your assessment    Step 2: Click on “Add-to-Profile” button from your student account    Step 3: Fill out the form!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal trainer plan</title>
      <link>/regular/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/regular/</guid>
      <description>REGULAR Plan / twice a week   REGULAR PLAN   Improve your level of English proficiency, twice a week with personal trainer from USA or UK.    REGULAR PLAN  Improve your level of English proficiency, twice a week with personal trainer from USA, UK or South Africa. Get started!   $120/month (cancel anytime)    25-minute lessons    Monthly assessments    Easily fits your personal schedule    All teachers are native speakers, experienced &amp; certified    Homework assigned by your teacher after each lesson      Recommended if you want to quickly assess your English skills, both reading and listening.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scratch cards</title>
      <link>/cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cards/</guid>
      <description>Scratch Cards   Add your LAL SET Certificate to your LinkedIn Profile  With completion of your LAL SET, you will receive a personalized, official English certificate (view example). You can easily add your LAL SET Certificate URL to your LinkedIn profile - in 3 easy steps!   Step 1: Take the LAL SET    Step 2: Click on “Add-to-Profile” button from the LAL SET Results Page    Step 3: Fill out the form!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>